[Music]
Hello friends Nashad and you are watching my
personal experience Poland friends in today's
video I will give you an update of the entire process for Slovenia
and a
lot of people contact me for Slovenia, a lot of
people don't know about the process
and they don't know when their TRC will come, they do
n't know the time, they do
n't know about biometric, I am getting a lot of such
calls even now just five
minutes ago I got a video call from a guy
who was from Bangladesh
and his TRC is not coming, he does
n't know how the process is going on, so I
thought that today in this video I will give you the
complete update of Slovenia,
you must have seen a lot of my videos about
Slovenia, like guys many people
's TRC has come and they are flying, Manoj Bhai has gone yesterday too,
Manoj Bhai had a flight yesterday,
he has taken it, so today let's talk
about Slovenia, so friends see the
process of Slovenia is very
good because it does
n't require a back statement, today I will tell you first
what are the documents  What is required and what is not
required? If someone
asks you for a different document according to this video of mine, then you
can question him that there is nothing like that. So
first let's talk serial wise,
like suppose the first option is that
you asked someone to get some work done
and they took your documents
and whether they took the work video or not is a
different matter, like in mine, work video is
required, so suppose you
gave the work video and you gave the documents,
now you are selected, from the front
you get a message that you are selected, now let's
start your process, okay, so
when the process starts, at the
time of starting your process, they will first ask you
what documents will be required and what will
not be required, I will tell you that because
I have seen even outside the embassy that there is a system of
misleading a lot of people or taking money,
this is a system of taking money, get the
documents made which are not required,
so that is a system of taking money, now
as in this everyone knows that
insurance is required to go to Slon,
but brother, insurance is not required in Slovenia,
insurance is not required.
I've seen people also bring insurance after the MC,
and they've also filled out the application form and given
them this, that, and that. There's nothing like that.
You only need four documents to
begin with: your
passport, your education certificate,
experience certificate, and the PCC. The
PCC that's mostly used is
from the local police station, which is your
direct PCC, not from the passport office. There's
a PCC that you
apply for by going to the passport office. There's a
PCC that you apply for directly by going to your nearest police station, the
police station. It can
also be applied online. There's
no need for an appointment, etc. That's the PCC that's being used.
If someone has one, they
use the PCC from the passport office to start the process, but they
need it later. Now, let's talk about
one of these four documents: a passport copy. The
method for getting a copy is
different. One copy is that you get the
front and back done directly, and that's
your copy. But in this process, you have to get a
copy of the passport.  There is
one photo of yours,
or suppose there is a page with a photo on the top and
two photos on the back side, one with
your passport photo on which you
write your wallet date and one with your
address at the bottom. Now turn the page to the back, on the
top side of the back side, the Ashoka
light, the Ashoka light, is
so big, when you
open the passport, that will be the copy and the bottom portion will be
blank, the stamps for your hostel will be placed
there, the hostel stamps will be placed
there, this is the method of getting
your passport copied.
Now the passport is done, you have to get these four things uploaded - your education
certificate, experience certificate and
PCC. All four
things will be postal, after being uploaded
your process is done, that is, if
someone tells you to
send me the PDF of the document, get it done by postal later, okay, get
your hostel done later,
send me the PDF, make them and get the PCC done
later, there is no issue, but
your process can be started on those documents, there is no
problem  Even if you get it done
earlier, there will still be no problem.
I have told you an option that if
by chance you are out or you are getting late,
then you can give your documents in PDF format to them and you
can get the hostel done later. There is no problem
in starting the process. So now what happens is that
you have given the documents,
after giving the documents, whatever will be their time period for
working, your agency, your friends,
your colleagues, whoever it is,
when your documents start, your process gets
started, then
in at least one and a half to two months,
you will also get the contract and a single copy will come on
which your photo will be pasted and it will be
written in Slovenian language and there will be such a tag on it, you get
these two documents of Slovenia and
after that you get the date,
okay, the date is also of the embassy, ​​there is
no BFS in it, you have to go
directly to the Slovenian embassy
in Delhi for the Slovenian process,
okay, it is hardly possible from the metro station  If
you give Rs. 50, they will take it off at the embassy. The
process starts by giving you that document.
You will get
your employment contract on which the salary is written. It is of
five to six pages.
After that, you will get a single paper on which your
photo will also be there. You will get the date. Now
what do you have to do after the date comes? You have to go and do the biometric on that same date. There are
two points in this also. For the
trades people, that is, the skilled
workers, the trades people were not being interviewed earlier.
Four months ago,
interviews were not being conducted. Now,
interviews are being conducted. When you get the date, it is
written in it - this date, this name, date of
birth of the person and in that,
you have your fingerprint on this date. I will try and
show it to you right now on the side. This date
comes to you like this. I will
show you in the screenshot. It will have the name, date of
birth and the date of fingerprint.
You should come to do the fingerprint on this date. Now, there are two
issues. Some people get the date,
after that the embassy is calling you for the interview.
Then you will get an email after 10, 15 days, 20 days or a
month that you have to come on this date.  Some
people have to come for the interview,
fingerprint plus biometric sorry, biometric
plus interview,
appointments for biometric plus interview are also coming like this, that is, there will be
an email in which
your name will be there, your date of birth and your
timing of visiting the embassy, ​​it will be
written in it, biometric plus
interview, this means that all your work has to be done at one time, there will be
biometric as well, the
interview will also be on the same day, now
if in whose email it is written biometric, that means
his fingerprint is there but there will be
no interview, the interview may come later or may
not come at all, but for the trade people it will come,
now for the hotel liners, that is, chefs or
bartenders or waiters, their
interview may also not come, there is a high chance that it will
not come, there is a very less
chance that it may come, but for the trade people it will
come, this is your interview, the whole
matter of documents is over, now after the
interview, after the interview you have to wait,
your agency will tell you whether you have passed
or failed, at the time of interview the
watchman will give you a slip, your name will be in the list,
you will get your
email address, your passport in the slip
Enter your number and phone number and submit it to them, it is
also taken when you go inside, you will come to
know about it, then they can give you an email embassy on the mail itself, it
also tells your company
that this person has failed or rejected, whatever, then
after that they will update you that
yes you have passed, if you fail in the interview,
by chance they reject you, then from now on
your process is now
dependent on your company, what will they do, the
person who gets selected, whose
interview is cleared, they have to
wait for the TRC, now what happens
when you pass the interview,
after passing the company tells you that yes brother you have passed,
after passing you have to wait
for the TRC, now the mail which you have given, you may get an
email to receive the TRC, you should
come at this time after biometric,
after 10, 15 days, 20 days keep an eye on your mail
and in the same mail, you have to
go there at the same time and
collect your TRC, now when you
go to collect the TRC, the most point thing  Let me tell you one more thing
so that you do not face any problem, at the time of TRC,
take Paytm on your phone because inside you have to pay 1150 Indian Rupees
and you get the TRC,
if you do not have it then you will be
sent to the bank and the bank is quite far away, you may have to stand in
line there and you will have to go by auto, you will have to stand in
line, so to avoid all this tension, take
Paytm on your phone. The officer who is taking the interview inside the Slovenia Embassy is like a fair-skinned person, he is completely bald, so
his way of talking is a bit
strong, that means if we
go in our language, then there is a stick guy,
that type of brother, he is an officer, his style
will be, but you people should not worry because
many people get worried by the name of interview,
hey the interview is over, what should you do now,
prepare for your documents, memorize all the
information that is in your documents,
your company and your salary,
in many interviews brother 2022 questions are being asked
and it is done in two ways, one is that
first you  Writing means you will give the paper and
in the paper you will sit like in a class,
fill your paper and
give it to them, after that they will send you out, then
after some time they will call you, the
officer will talk to you and he will talk to
you in English and there is no need to take tension,
talk comfortably, think as much as you can
but do not take too much time, if
they asked the question today you think you will answer tomorrow, it is
not like that, try to answer a little quickly
and give the answer in short, there is
one thing that is good talk, means
talk less and talk well in short,
you have given the complete answer, you have to talk like this, you should
not go on for a long time, just if
they ask why are you going then
you tell him that we are going for a job,
who is yours there, you tell him that there is no
one there, you do not have to think much, that means
answer comfortably with a completely free mind, there is no
tension, you will pass, Inshallah
everyone is passing, if there is any problem
then your agency is behind you, you talk to them,
okay, now I have given so much information,
I do not think, maybe there is something left, if nothing
comes to my mind  If you have any questions, please
comment in the comment box and I will also reply,
Inshallah I will make a video. Okay, so right now
I will make many videos of the process of Slovenia. You guys keep asking,
Inshallah I will keep making videos so that
you guys get benefited and you guys do
n't face any problem. I have clarified many things in it
like about the money,
how much payment you have to make after going inside, what kind of
50 documents are there, how will the
copy of the passport be there, I have clarified all these things for
you. If
something goes out of my mind, still you guys
can ask in the comments. Those who talk to me, please do so and
I will reply as well. So
friends, Inshallah, it was an attempt to tell you guys
something good about Slovenia
and I will make the next video for you as well.
Inshallah, I will meet
you again in the next video. Like, share, subscribe to Nashad Bhai's channel.
Share it as much as possible so that those who are doing the
process can get help. And
your love is with me. All of you
brothers, once again I will apologize to
anyone if it happens to me,
brothers, okay.  Inshallah, we will meet
again in the next video, both Shad Allah
Hafiz